Curriculum Vitae

Name: Vaibhav Chaudhary Cell No: +91 7310166218

Add: Sector 17 Indira Nagar Lucknow

Email: vibhufrontdev@gmail.com

Objectives:

To obtain challenging and rewarding web developer position in with growth and learning opportunities in supportive, challenging work environment that would take advantage of my job experience.

Techinical Skills:

Bootstrap, Tailwind, Worldpress, Elementor, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, Jquery, Scss, Less Css, Figma, Illistrator Microsoft Windows (Windows 7, Windows 10)

Summary of Experience:

Smart Web Professional with 2.3 year of experience in the development of Web Applications and other using HTML,css and bootstrap. I aspire to be associated with a progressive firm wherein I can apply my knowledge and skills in developing business applications and thereby contribute towards the growth of the organization.

Educational Qualification:

Qualification : **Diploma**

University: Government Polytechnic Lucknow

Professional Experience:

Organization: Ommune IT Solution Pvt Ltd

Designation: Web Developer

Duration : Dec 2022 - Apr 2023

Organization : Digi Epitome Pvt Ltd

Designation: Web Developer

Duration : Dec 2022 - Apr 2023

Organization: Ferry Infotech Pvt Ltd

Designation : Web Developer

Duration : Mar 2022 - Nov 2022

Organization: Manak Analatics and Development

Designation: Web Developer

Duration : Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Organization: Edugorilla Community Pvt Ltd

Designation : Computer Operator Duration : Dec 2020 - Nov 2020

Project Experience Highlights

Project Name : Landformsgroup.com

Url : https://landformsgroup.com/
Technology : Html, JS and Jquery, CI
Role : Design(Html) , Devlopement

Project Name : Mayasoftech

Url : https://mayasoftech.com/
Technology : Html, JS and Jquery, CI
Role : Design(Html) , Devlopement

Project Name : **SMUbuliders**

Url : https://smubuilders.com/

Technology : Html, JS and Jquery, scss,Laravel Role : Design(Html) , Devlopement

Project Name : Unilifeinfo

Url : https://unilifeinfo.com/
Technology : Html, JS and Jquery

Policy (Html)

Role : Design(Html)

Project Name : **Stormwaves**

Url : https://stormwaves.org/
Technology : https://stormwaves.org/
Technology : https://stormwaves.org/

Role : Design(Html)

Project Name : Visual Notes

Url : https://visualnotes.com/

Technology : Html, Bootstrap, JS and Jquery

Role : Design(Html)

Project Name : Coachoptima

Url : https://app.coachoptima.com/
Technology : Html, JS and Jquery, scss

Role : Design(Html)

Project Name : YOHRM

Url: https://yohrm.com/

Technology : Html, Bootstrap and Jquery

Role : Design(Html)

Project Name : **Vedic Pupil**

Url : https://app.vedicpupil.com/

Technology : Html, PHP, MySql, JS and Jquery ,Laravel

Role : Design(Html) and Testing

Personal Details:

Date of birth 28 January 2000 Father's name : Mr. Dileep Chaudhary
Mother's name : Mrs. Shanti
Hobbies : Driving, coding ,learning novel
Languages known : English, Hindi

Declaration:

I solemnly declare that the information given above are true to the best of my knowledge and nothing is incorrect.

Date:

Place: Lucknow (Vaibhav Chaudhary)